It doesn't look like an accidental fall.
Sir, please don't dissect my dad.
He's already mangled enough.
Please,
let him go in one piece.
Stop investigating.
Don't dissect him.
Han, a forensic doctor's scalpel
only recognizes evidence,
not tears.
Han, what's wrong?
You look so pale.
I'm fine.
Star, time is running out.
How exactly did she die?
She couldn't think straight
and hanged herself, right?
Just say it, and this will all be over.
Han, don't blame yourself.
But remember,
there can be no personal feelings
under the scalpel.
Master! Master!
No. A survival game
would never kindly offer
a safe shortcut to clear the level.
This is a play.
If I follow her wishes
and say it was a hanging,
it means I completely accept
the script written by the villain,
becoming a marionette on this stage.
The follow-up will only lead
to a deadly trap.
The only way out is to flip the table
and forcefully tear a rift in the plot.
The deceased was first knocked unconscious
by a blunt force trauma to the back of the head,
followed by strangulation.
The killer knocked her out first,
then strangled her with a piano wire,
disguising it as a hanging.
This is a homicide.
Han, watch out!
Xiao Han, get down!
You refuse a toast
only to drink a forfeit.
Since you won't play along,
you can all die on the stage!
Hurry! While she's dispersed,
follow me into the secret room.
Once she gathers her evil aura,
not even the gods can save you.
There's a secret room like this
behind the dressing room?
If the Marshal wants to live,
do not trust the Star beside you.
At midnight, the Star
will surely take
the Marshal's heart blood.
The real demon is...
Li Xiang wrote these words
by biting her finger.
She warned us with her life.
The dead end in the third act
is forcing me to act.
The Star, the Marshal...
Does this mean Han will kill Yang?
This is the script for the third act.
The so-called destined person
by the system
has always been...
How are you so familiar
with this secret passage?
What exactly is Su Lingyue?
Because I am the only surviving
stagehand of this troupe
from a hundred years ago.
Su Lingyue is a theatrical fiend
who died on this stage a century ago.
She feeds on resentment
by dragging living people in to perform
deadly plays of mutual slaughter.
If you had lied along with her just now,
you would have ended up like me,
slowly turning into marionettes
for her to control.
So when I called out homicide just now,
it was like forcefully
tearing up her script,
forcing her to reveal her true form.
You broke the second act
and bought a glimmer of hope.
But once midnight strikes,
the third act will forcefully begin.
One of you is destined to die.
Follow me.
These forty-seven pairs
are the audience out front.
They were all once living people
just like you.
Now they are part of this stage.
What are these?
We can't perform Act III.
It's a dead end.
We are all puppets.
But we still can't get out.
The theater eats people.
Never to be reincarnated.
These are the last words
left by past lead actors.
Everyone was
eventually forced
to kill their Marshal in Act III.
And after killing him?
Did they clear the game?
After killing the Marshal,
the actor's soul is trapped
on stage forever.
The Marshal becomes a spectator
in the audience.
An endless cycle.
Never to be freed.
I get it.
The real demon isn't Su Lingyue at all.
If not Su Lingyue, who else could it be?
These paintings... 47 Marshals.
Different eras,
different clothes.
But they are all sitting
in the exact same armchair.
The armchair.
This chair, having absorbed
the blood of 47 generations,
is the true heart of this theater.
Young man, you have a sharp eye.
To think you could see through this.
When Su Lingyue died tragically,
all her resentment and blood
poured into this chair.
It is the true man-eating demon.
This symbol... Could it be Master?
Hanzi, if you can read this,
it means I didn't escape this game either.
Don't trust the system's rules.
The real key to breaking the game...
Fifteen minutes until midnight.
Act III of Blood Sacrifice
in the Pear Garden is about to begin.
Preparation time is over.
Marshal, please take your seat.
Actor, please take the stage.
Yang,